





Summary

Jump to Section

An MBA and PMP, CSM, AWS certified professional with 10+ years of experience in project management and presales support for IT software, Cloud and IT infrastructure solutions.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Proven track record of leading and successfully delivering projects of worth more than \$1 million, resulting in 10%+ increase in operational efficiency, and 15%+ improved customer satisfaction.

Work Experience

ICICI Bank as Project Manager-IT Apr 2016 to Till Date

Manage & deliver strategic IT projects through both waterfall and agile methodologies Contribute towards evaluation and design phases of technical IT & cloud projects and lead planning and execution Coordinate with cross-functional stakeholders & multiple vendors to execute the project work Keep track of all ongoing projects' progress and facilitate periodic review calls with the leadership team Creating presentations, project documents, project trackers, progress reports, cost-benefit analysis, closure reports, etc. for strategic transformative projects

Evaluate bid proposals from vendors and provide recommendations to the leadership team. Ensure compliance with change management and security & hardening guidelines, to mitigate technical and operational risk

Ericsson India Pvt. Ltd., as System Engineer Oct 2013 to Apr 2014

Analyze customer requirements and propose design & solution for many complex VoLTE, IMS, and RCS deals across the globe

Perform feature gap analysis from incoming RFPs, discuss & review gaps with regional sales & product manager teams

Nokia Networks Pvt. Ltd as Solution Specialist Feb 2010 to Sep 2013

Collaborate with regional teams to understand the current technical environment, key business drivers/issues and propose solutions to fulfill the requirements of customers

Proportional responses to global PEI REC and REP related to CSCE HSS RCRE and IM MME and CSS

Recommend technical responses to global RFI, RFQ and RFP related to CSCF, HSS, PCRF, eNUM, MME and GGSN

^ Back to Top

41

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

PG: MBA/PGDM (FINANCE AND BANKING) from NIIT UNIVERSITY in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: AWS solution architect associate Certified Scrum Master

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Firewall		
IMS, RCS, VoLTE		
MME, S/P GW, GGSN		
SDN, NFV		
DHCP, DNS		
Linux & Python		
WIRESHARK		
HPITSM		
CISCO DCNM		
PUTTY		
NETMON		
SOLARWINDS		
VMWARE WORKSTATION PRO		
AWS	2019	1 Year(s)
JIRA, MS Office, MS Projects		
VirtualBox, vCenter, Confluence		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Cloud Adoption for Networking Monitoring (SNMP) Setup

Client: ICICI Bank

Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Mumbai Duration: Feb 2019 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Role: Project Leader Team Size: 6

Skill Used: Project Management, Cloud Computing

Role Description: * Contribution in designing the architecture and creation & maintenance of VPC, security groups, route tables. NACLs. etc

Ensuring compliance with all security guidelines to mitigate technical risk

Project Details: This project is about building the monitoring application setup on cloud, following the cloud security and high availability best practices.

Project Title: SDWAN Implementation

Client: ICICI Bank

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2018 - Till Date Role: Sr. Project Leader Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Team Size: 20

Skill Used: Project Management, Networking

Role Description: * Leading the overall project including all deliverables like SDWAN appliances setup, link delivery, new branch office rollout and migration of existing branches

Risk analysis along with business and technical network teams

Project Details: This project is about migrating the traditional WAN network to SDWAN which is a software-defined approach to managing the wide-area network

Project Title: WAN Digital Transformation

Client: ICICI Bank

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2017 - Till Date Project Location: Mumbai Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Role: Project Leader Team Size: 12

Skill Used: Project Management

Role Description: * Requirement Gathering, POC & Requirement Freeze for the changes.

- Assisted business teams in devising testing scenarios & performing unit testing

Conducted Project Review meetings for daily updates on the project dashboard induding link dalian anangga Project Details: vvan management tool is built to automate the ICICI wan operations including link delivery process, branch monitoring, asset management and service provider payment process; for 5000+ ICICI branches and DC.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.